pandahallstock.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy- Help Center

Nbeads Support   
posted this on Apr 15, 2014 at 07:01 PM

  * **1\. Our Commitment to Privacy**

Your privacy is of great importance. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and your different choices of the way your information is collected and used.

**2\. The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Nbeads.com  
For the pages that you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials, the types of business and personal information collected at these pages are as follows.

   > Business Name  
   > Contact Name  
   > Address  
   > Email address  
   > Phone number  
   > PayPal information

**3\. The Way We Use Information**

The information you provided and we collected is only used to complete your order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.  
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.  
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers.  
We'll need your email address if you wish to receive our newsletters or use our service to contact a retailer. All other information is optional. Each newsletter will tell you how to unsubscribe if you want to stop getting our mailings or need to change your email address.  
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**4.   Direct Marketing**

We may contact you from time to time with a view to providing the latest information on our products and services / member program. If you do not wish to receive these updates, please login at http:www.nbeads.com to unsubscribe. Alternatively, you may click the unsubscribe link as shown in our electronic promotional materials; or can write to us via e-mail to sales@nbeads.com or via mail at HuiYuan 2-908, District A, Technology Park of Wuhan University, East Lake High-Tech Development Zone, Wuhan City, Hubei Province, China or via calling at (0086) 027 59710538. In accordance with the statutory requirements, we will honor your request not to use your Personal Data for the purposes of direct marketing. Unless otherwise instructed as per the above, we may use any of your Personal Data collected in the normal course of our business for direct marketing purposes.  

**5\. Accessing Personal Data**

You have full control and ability to correct or edit your Personal Data at any time, including whether you want us to contact you about direct marketing purpose, VIP promotional offers and new products and services or deletion of your VIP membership online account. You may request your right of access or right of correction by logging in at http://www.nbeads.com. Alternatively, you may click the unsubscribe link as shown in our electronic promotional materials; or can write to us via e-mail to sales@nbeads.com or via mail at HuiYuan 2-908, District A, Technology Park of Wuhan University, East Lake High-Tech Development Zone, Wuhan City, Hubei Province, China or via calling at (0086) 027 59710538. We will upon satisfying itself of the authenticity and validity of the access or correction request, make every endeavor to comply with and respond to the request within the period set by the statutory requirement.

**6\. Our Commitment to Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

  * Was this answer helpful?
